Guide to the Henry S. Kaplan Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Miscellaneous Materials, Series 8
  - 3x5" index cards from a file cabinet reflecting drawer and tab separators.
    - Drawer Name: Adrenal, General Biochemistry, cont.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 8 - Protein Synthesis and Protein Structure
      - Drawer 1, Tab 9 - C-Reactive and other acute phase reactive proteins
      - Drawer 1, Tab 10 - Lipoproteins
      - Drawer 1, Tab 11 - Amino Acids - Metab., and activation, Biosynthesis
      - Drawer 1, Tab 12 - Lipids, Steroids
      - Drawer 1, Tab 13 - Mucopolysaccharides; mucoproteins, cell wall
      - Drawer 1, Tab 14 - Miscellaneous
    - Drawer Name: Biochemical Effects of Radiation, cont.
      - Drawer 2, Tab 1 - Biochemical Effects of Radiation
      - Drawer 2, Tab 2 - Rad. Chemistry of H2O; inorg. comp.
      - Drawer 2, Tab 3 - Proteins, Amino Acids, Peptides
      - Drawer 2, Tab 4 - RNA
      - Drawer 2, Tab 5 - Purine, Pyrmidine Bases, Nucleocides, Nucleotides
      - Drawer 2, Tab 6 - UV Photochemistry of Nuc. Acids and Bases
      - Drawer 2, Tab 7 - Photoreactivation Repair of DNA
      - Drawer 2, Tab 8 - DNA Structure, Viscosity, etc.
      - Drawer 2, Tab 9 - Enzymes and Inhibitors of Repair
      - Drawer 2, Tab 10 - Mutants and Repair
      - Drawer 2, Tab 11 - N.A. Content and Degradation
      - Drawer 2, Tab 12 - Transforming or Primer DNA Activity
      - Drawer 2, Tab 13 - Nucleoprotein
      - Drawer 2, Tab 14 - DNA Synthesis
      - Drawer 2, Tab 15 -
      - Drawer 2, Tab 16 - Other Enzymes
      - Drawer 2, Tab 17 - Miscellaneous
      - Drawer 2, Tab 18 - Polymers, Model
      - Drawer 2, Tab 19 - Phosphorylation and ATP Synthesis
    - Drawer Name: Biological Effects of Radiation
      - Drawer 3, Tab 1 - Biologic Effects of Radiation - Reviews
      - Drawer 3, Tab 2 - B.E.R. - Sensitizers, Chemical
      - Drawer 3, Tab 3 - Oxygen; Nitric Oxide; Nitroxides
      - Drawer 3, Tab 4 - B.E.R. - Reoxygenation
      - Drawer 3, Tab 5 - Anoxia, Hypothermia, Exercise
      - Drawer 3, Tab 6 - B.E.R.: Acute lethal effects
      - Drawer 3, Tab 7 - B.E.R. - Colchiline
      - Drawer 3, Tab 8 - Preprotective Agents: Cysteine, GSH, etc.
      - Drawer 3, Tab 9 - Polyhydroxyl Alcohols; CHO
      - Drawer 3, Tab 10 - Hormones
      - Drawer 3, Tab 11 - Misc. Pharmacol Agents
      - Drawer 3, Tab 12 - Spleen and Marrow, Shielding, Implants, Extracts
      - Drawer 3, Tab 13 - Human Total Body RX (Leukemia, graft)
      - Drawer 3, Tab 14 - B.E.R. - Blood and Blood Forming Tissues
      - Drawer 3, Tab 15 - B.E.R. - Theoretical
      - Drawer 3, Tab 16 - Biological Effects of Internal Emitters
      - Drawer 3, Tab 17 - B.E.R. - Effects on ______ Tissues
      - Drawer 3, Tab 18 - B.E.R. - Let and RBE
      - Drawer 3, Tab 19 - B.E.R. - Misc.
      - Drawer 3, Tab 20 - B.E.R. - Genetic Effects, Mutations
      - Drawer 3, Tab 21 - B.E.R. - Effects of Fetus
      - Drawer 3, Tab 22 - B.E.R. - Chimeras Immunol.
      - Drawer 3, Tab 23 - B.E.R. - Extracorporeal Irradiation
      - Drawer 3, Tab 24 - Dose Response, Fractionation, Periodic
      - Drawer 3, Tab 25 - Local Irrad.
      - Drawer 3, Tab 26 - Nutrition, Incl. Vitamins, Folic Acid
      - Drawer 3, Tab 27 - Transfusion, Infusion of Blood, Serum, etc.
      - Drawer 3, Tab 28 - Parabiosis
      - Drawer 3, Tab 29 - Flavonoids
      - Drawer 3, Tab 30 - Physiol. Changes during Rad. Death
    - Drawer Name: Biological Effects of Radiation, Biophysics, Blood-Forming Tissues, Bone Tumors
      Section 1: Biological Effects of Radiation
      - Drawer 4, Tab 31 - B.E.R. Mammalian Cells in vitro
      - Drawer 4, Tab 32 - Mutant Mammalian Cells and Repair, etc.
      - Drawer 4, Tab 33 - B.E.R. - Effects on Cell Cycle Kinetics; Prolif. Rates
      - Drawer 4, Tab 34 - B.E.R. Mammalian Cells in vivo
      - Drawer 4, Tab 35 - B.E.R. - Nonmammal Vertebrates
      - Drawer 4, Tab 36 - B.E.R. - Invertebrates
      - Drawer 4, Tab 37 - B.E.R. Mitotic Inhibition
      - Drawer 4, Tab 38 - Partial-Cell Micro-Beam Irradiation
      - Drawer 4, Tab 39 - Recovery, Repair in Mammalian Cells
      - Drawer 4, Tab 40 - B.E.R. Plant Cells
      - Drawer 4, Tab 41 - B.E.R.- UV, Photo Reactivation
      - Drawer 4, Tab 42 - B.E.R. - Photo Inactivation
      - Drawer 4, Tab 43 - B.E.R. - Viruses
      - Drawer 4, Tab 44 - B.E.R. - Isotope Suicide
      - Drawer 4, Tab 45 - Bacteria, X-Rays, and UV
      - Drawer 4, Tab 46 - Yeasts, X-Rays
      - Drawer 4, Tab 47 - Protozoa, Ameba
      - Drawer 4, Tab 48 - Strain & Species Differences
      - Drawer 4, Tab 49 - B.E.R. - Cytologic Studies
      - Drawer 4, Tab 50 - Age, Sex, Weight, misc. Environ. Factors
      - Drawer 4, Tab 51 - B.E.R. - Adrenal, Pituitary
      - Drawer 4, Tab 52 - B.E.R. - Infection
      - Drawer 4, Tab 53 - B.E.R. - Late Renal Lesions
      - Drawer 4, Tab 54 - B.E.R.: Longevity
      - Drawer 4, Tab 55 - B.E.R. - Gonads
      - Drawer 4, Tab 56 - B.E.R. - Effects on Blood Vessels
      - Drawer 4, Tab 57 - B.E.R. - GI Tract
      - Drawer 4, Tab 58 - B.E.R. - Skin & Appendages
      - Drawer 4, Tab 59 - B.E.R. - Nervous System
    - Drawer Name: Biological Effects of Radiation, Biophysics, Blood-Forming Tissues, Bone Tumors, cont.
      Section 2: Biophysics
      - Drawer 4, Tab 1 - Biophysics
      - Drawer 4, Tab 2 - Bladders Exper. Tumors
    - Drawer Name: Biological Effects of Radiation, Biophysics, Blood-Forming Tissues, Bone Tumors, cont.
      Section 3: Blood Forming Tissues
      - Drawer 4, Tab 1 - Blood and Hemopoiesis Exper.
      - Drawer 4, Tab 2 - Bone Marrow Transplants
      - Drawer 4, Tab 3 - Blood Formation -Megakaryocytes and Platelets
    - Drawer Name: Biological Effects of Radiation, Biophysics, Blood-Forming Tissues, Bone Tumors, cont.
      Section 4: Bone Tumors
      - Drawer 4, Tab 1 - Bone - Exper. Tumors
      - Drawer 4, Tab 2 - Brain - Exper. Tumors
    - Drawer Name: Carcinogenesis Viral
      - Drawer 5, Tab 1 - Carc. - Viruses - Gen. and Reviews
      - Drawer 5, Tab 2 - Carc. Viruses - Rous
      - Drawer 5, Tab 3 - Carc. Virus - Adenoviruses
      - Drawer 5, Tab 4 - CA. Viruses - SV 40
      - Drawer 5, Tab 5 - Human and Primate Papoviruses
      - Drawer 5, Tab 6 - CA. Viruses - Polyoma
      - Drawer 5, Tab 7 - Papilloma Viruses
      - Drawer 5, Tab 8 - CA. Virus - Feline Sarco
      - Drawer 5, Tab 9 - Rat Sarcoma Viruses
      - Drawer 5, Tab 10 - CA Viruses - Murine (MSV) Moloney/Harvey/Sarcoma Virus
      - Drawer 5, Tab 11 - CA Viruses - Lucke, Frog Renal CA
      - Drawer 5, Tab 12 - Marek's Dis. Virus
      - Drawer 5, Tab 13 - Primate Herpes Viruses and Lymphoma-Leukemia
      - Drawer 5, Tab 14 - Herpes Simplex Virus
      - Drawer 5, Tab 15 - Carc. Virus - E.B. Virus
      - Drawer 5, Tab 16 - Carc. Virus - Osteosarcoma
      - Drawer 5, Tab 17 - CA. Viruses - Mammary
      - Drawer 5, Tab 18 - CA. Viruses - Shope
      - Drawer 5, Tab 19 - CA. Viruses - Electron Microscopy
      - Drawer 5, Tab 20 - Poss. Human Tumor Viruses
      - Drawer 5, Tab 21 - CA. Viruses - RNA, DNA
      - Drawer 5, Tab 22 - Carc. Virus - Neutroblastoma
      - Drawer 5, Tab 23 - CA. Viruses - Misc. Sources
    - Drawer Name: Carcinogenesis Other
      - Drawer 6, Tab 1 - Carc. Historical
      - Drawer 6, Tab 2 - Carcinogenesis: General - Theoretical
      - Drawer 6, Tab 3 - Carc. - Genetic Mech incl. Somatic Mutation
      - Drawer 6, Tab 4 - Mutation; DNA Damage and Repair by Chem. and Phys. Agents
      - Drawer 6, Tab 5 - Transforming Genes by Transfection Assay or Blot Hybridization, etc.
      - Drawer 6, Tab 6 - Biochemical Alterations in Transformed Cells.
      - Drawer 6, Tab 7 - Carcinogenesis: Biology of Growth, Control Mech.
      - Drawer 6, Tab 8 - Heterogeneity
      - Drawer 6, Tab 9 - Tumor Angiogenesis Factor
      - Drawer 6, Tab 10 - CA. - Surface Membrane Changes
      - Drawer 6, Tab 11 - Aneuploidy, Markers, Translocations
      - Drawer 6, Tab 12 - Chromosomal Control of Malif. Phenotype
      - Drawer 6, Tab 13 - Carcinogenesis Immune Reactions
      - Drawer 6, Tab 14 - Carcinogenesis; Stages, Initiation and Promotion
      - Drawer 6, Tab 15 - Proteases; Plasminogen, Activator in Transformed Cells
      - Drawer 6, Tab 16 - Carc. - in vitro
      - Drawer 6, Tab 17 - Carc. Hydrocarbons
      - Drawer 6, Tab 18 - Carc. - Hormones
      - Drawer 6, Tab 19 - Carc. - Polymers, Films, Metal Foils
      - Drawer 6, Tab 20 - Carc. - A20 Dyes, AAF, Acetamides
      - Drawer 6, Tab 21 - Carc. - Urethan
      - Drawer 6, Tab 22 - Carc. - Plant Tumors
      - Drawer 6, Tab 23 - Carc. - Radiation
      - Drawer 6, Tab 24 - Carc. - Drugs
      - Drawer 6, Tab 25 - Aflatoxins
      - Drawer 6, Tab 26 - Cycasin
      - Drawer 6, Tab 27 - Carc. - Nitrosoureas, Nitrosamines
      - Drawer 6, Tab 28 - Miscellaneous Carcinogens
      - Drawer 6, Tab 29 - Carcinogenesis: Human Extracts
      - Drawer 6, Tab 30 - Carcinogenesis: Mathematical Models
      - Drawer 6, Tab 31 - Carcinogenesis - Host Susceptibility Factors
      - Drawer 6, Tab 32 - Co-Carcinogenesis, Potentiation
      - Drawer 6, Tab 33 - Anticarcinogenesis
      - Drawer 6, Tab 34 - Carcinogenesis - Misc.
      - Drawer 6, Tab 35 - Carcinogenesis: Metabolism of Agents
      - Drawer 6, Tab 36 - Carcinogenesis: Relation of Structure and Activity
      - Drawer 6, Tab 37 - Cervix - Exper. CA
      - Drawer 6, Tab 38 - Colchicine
    - Drawer Name: Cell Culture, Cytology, Cytochemistry, Cytogenetics
      Section 1: Cell Culture
      - Drawer 7, Tab 1 - Culture in Vitro: Reviews
      - Drawer 7, Tab 2 - Culture in Vitro: Historical
      - Drawer 7, Tab 3 - Culture in Vitro: Synchrony
      - Drawer 7, Tab 4 - Culture in Vitro: Gradients, Cell Separation Techniques
      - Drawer 7, Tab 5 - Cytology, Stain Tech., Morphology
      - Drawer 7, Tab 6 - Culture: Freezing, Thawing, Preservation
      - Drawer 7, Tab 7 - Culture in Vitro: Media, Methods
      - Drawer 7, Tab 8 - Culture; Organ and Diffusion Chamber Tech.
      - Drawer 7, Tab 9 - T.C. - Markers, Mutants, etc.
      - Drawer 7, Tab 10 - Colony - Stimulating Factors Inducers of Hemat. Differentation
      - Drawer 7, Tab 11 - Cell Growth Factors: FGF, EGF, NGF, TCGF, etc.
      - Drawer 7, Tab 12 - Culture - Chemostats, Product Stas
      - Drawer 7, Tab 13 - Culture - Normal Cells and Strains
      - Drawer 7, Tab 14 - Culture - Blood Cells, Marrow, and Related Tissues
      - Drawer 7, Tab 15 - Established Lines; Non-Human
      - Drawer 7, Tab 16 - Culture In Vitro: Growth Kinetics
      - Drawer 7, Tab 17 - Culture In Vitro: Infection
      - Drawer 7, Tab 18 - Culture In Vitro: Substrates, Feeder Layers
      - Drawer 7, Tab 19 - Culture: Contact Inhibtion
      - Drawer 7, Tab 20 - Culture: Ploidy, Transformation
      - Drawer 7, Tab 21 - Culture: Effects of Chemical Agents on Growth and Cytology
      - Drawer 7, Tab 22 - Culture: Plant Cells
      - Drawer 7, Tab 23 - Culture in Vitro: Metabolic and Enzymatic Activity
    - Drawer Name: Cell Culture, Cytology, Cytochemistry, Cytogenetics, cont.
      Section 2: Cytology
    - Drawer Name: Cell Culture, Cytology, Cytochemistry, Cytogenetics, cont.
      Section 3: Cytochemistry
      - Drawer 7, Tab 1 - Chromatin Activity
    - Drawer Name: Cell Culture, Cytology, Cytochemistry, Cytogenetics, cont.
      Section 4: Cytogenetics
    - Drawer: Differentation, Genetics, Other
      - Drawer 8, Tab 1 - Differentiation
      - Drawer 8, Tab 2 - Embroyonal Carc., Teratocarcinoma
      - Drawer 8, Tab 3 - Embryogenesis, Incl. Teratogenesis
      - Drawer 8, Tab 4 - Genetic Control Mechanisms
      - Drawer 8, Tab 5 - Genetics Mammalian
      - Drawer 8, Tab 6 - Genetics, Microbial
      - Drawer 8, Tab 7 - Insertion Sequences, Transposons, Episomes
      - Drawer 8, Tab 8 - Cloning of Genes via Recombinant DNA
      - Drawer 8, Tab 9 - Genetics of Somatic Cells, Incl. Cell Fusion, etc.
      - Drawer 8, Tab 10 - Genetics, Protozoan
      - Drawer 8, Tab 11 - Histamine
      - Drawer 8, Tab 12 - Hepatography, Experimental
      - Drawer 8, Tab 13 - Hormones
      - Drawer 8, Tab 14 - Hormones - Thyroid
      - Drawer 8, Tab 15 - Hormones, General
      - Drawer 8, Tab 16 - Castration
      - Drawer 8, Tab 17 - Hormones-Male Sex
      - Drawer 8, Tab 18 - Progesterone
      - Drawer 8, Tab 19 - Hormones-Female Sex
      - Drawer 8, Tab 20 - Thyrotrophic Hormone
      - Drawer 8, Tab 21 - Hormones - Hypophysectomy
      - Drawer 8, Tab 22 - Pituitary Growth Hormone
      - Drawer 8, Tab 23 - Gonadotrophic
      - Drawer 8, Tab 24 - Pit. Lactogenic Hormone
      - Drawer 8, Tab 25 - Hormones - Chemistry
      - Drawer 8, Tab 26 - Hyaluronidase
    - Drawer name: Immunology
      - Drawer 9, Tab 1 - Immunology, General and Theoretical
      - Drawer 9, Tab 2 - Immunol. - Methods
      - Drawer 9, Tab 3 - T-Cell Hybridomas, Clones and Products
      - Drawer 9, Tab 4 - "Hybridoma" Antibodies
      - Drawer 9, Tab 5 - Lymphocyte Markers (T & B)
      - Drawer 9, Tab 6 - T Cell Markers
      - Drawer 9, Tab 7 - B Cell Markers
      - Drawer 9, Tab 8 - Plasma Cells
      - Drawer 9, Tab 9 - Lectins - Binding, Capping, Agglutination
      - Drawer 9, Tab 10 - Natural Killer Cells
      - Drawer 9, Tab 11 - Dendritic Cells
      - Drawer 9, Tab 12 - Macrophage Migration, Adherence, etc., in vitro
      - Drawer 9, Tab 13 - Culture of Macrophages and Monocytes; Cell Lines, etc.
      - Drawer 9, Tab 14 - Macrophages: Phagocytic Activity, Opsonins, etc.
      - Drawer 9, Tab 15 - "Activated" Macrophages
      - Drawer 9, Tab 16 - Lymphocytes - Macrophage Interactions
      - Drawer 9, Tab 17 - Lymphocytes - Immunocompetence, Circulation
      - Drawer 9, Tab 18 - Suppressor Cells
      - Drawer 9, Tab 19 - "Capping" - Surface Membrane Studies
      - Drawer 9, Tab 20 - "Tuftsin" - Spleen, other opsonizing factors
      - Drawer 9, Tab 21 - Immunologic Deficiency States - Human
      - Drawer 9, Tab 22 - Lymphokines
      - Drawer 9, Tab 23 - "Nude" Mice and Rats; Immunol. Function, Restoration
      - Drawer 9, Tab 24 - Graft vs. Host Reactions
      - Drawer 9, Tab 25 - Auto-Immune Mouse Strains
      - Drawer 9, Tab 26 - Organ and Tissue Transplants and Homografts
      - Drawer 9, Tab 27 - Immune Cytolysis
      - Drawer 10, Tab 1 - Blasoid Reactions in Vitro
      - Drawer 10, Tab 2 - Antilymphocyte Sera, Antithymocyte Sera
      - Drawer 10, Tab 3 - Tolerance
      - Drawer 10, Tab 4 - Transfer Factor
      - Drawer 10, Tab 5 - Transplantation Immunity
      - Drawer 10, Tab 6 - TLI and Immunosuppression
      - Drawer 10, Tab 7 - Local and WBI Radiation Effects
      - Drawer 10, Tab 8 - Antibody Symthesis in Vitro (Plaque Assay)
      - Drawer 10, Tab 9 - Immunoglobulins and their Genes
      - Drawer 10, Tab 10 - Antibody Conjugates
      - Drawer 10, Tab 11 - Immunotherapy, Exper.
      - Drawer 10, Tab 12 - Tumor Localization and Radiolabeled Antibody
      - Drawer 10, Tab 13 - Delayed Hypersensitivity
      - Drawer 10, Tab 14 - Autoimmune Diseases
      - Drawer 10, Tab 15 - Autosensitization in vitro; Cytoxicity, etc.
      - Drawer 10, Tab 16 - Genetic Control of the Immune Response
      - Drawer 10, Tab 17 - Immune Response Genes and Gene Products
      - Drawer 10, Tab 18 - Histocompatibility, Antigens; Genetics
      - Drawer 10, Tab 19 - Rhesus and Blood Group Antigenes (and Ab)
      - Drawer 10, Tab 20 - Embryonal Antigens
      - Drawer 10, Tab 21 - Ferritins
      - Drawer 10, Tab 22 - Tumor Antigens
      - Drawer 10, Tab 23 - Glycolipid Antigens
      - Drawer 10, Tab 24 - Leukocyte Antigens
      - Drawer 10, Tab 25 - Tissue/Organ-Specific (Differentiation) AG's
      - Drawer 10, Tab 26 - Sex Antigen
      - Drawer 10, Tab 27 - Antigen Binding and Processin
      - Drawer 10, Tab 28 - Fertility and Reproduction, Immunologic Effects
      - Drawer 10, Tab 29 - Complement and Complement Fixation
      - Drawer 10, Tab 30 - Antigen Chemistry
      - Drawer 10, Tab 31 - Immuno - Potentiators
      - Drawer 10, Tab 32 - Immunosuppressive Agents
      - Drawer 10, Tab 33 - Enhancement
      - Drawer 10, Tab 34 - Hemolytic Anemias, Coombs' Tests
      - Drawer 10, Tab 35 - Interferon
      - Drawer 10, Tab 36 - Miscellaneous
    - Drawer name: Leukemia and Lymphoma Experimental
      - Drawer 11, Tab 1 - Inflammation
      - Drawer 11, Tab 2 - Intestine - Exper. CA
      - Drawer 11, Tab 3 - Kidney-Exper.
      - Drawer 11, Tab 4 - Leukemia and Lymphonas, Exper.
      - Drawer 11, Tab 5 - Misc. incl. Reviews
      - Drawer 11, Tab 6 - Spontaneous
      - Drawer 11, Tab 7 - Induction-Base Analogs
      - Drawer 11, Tab 8 - Leuk. and Urethan
      - Drawer 11, Tab 9 - Induction: Radiation
      - Drawer 11, Tab 10 - Induction - Immuno. Genic
      - Drawer 11, Tab 11 - Induction: Hormones
      - Drawer 11, Tab 12 - Induction: Chem. Carcinogens
      - Drawer 11, Tab 13 - Chromosomes
      - Drawer 11, Tab 14 - Cytology and Histogenesis
      - Drawer 11, Tab 15 - Genetics
      - Drawer 11, Tab 16 - Morphology
      - Drawer 11, Tab 17 - Target Cell Studies
      - Drawer 11, Tab 18 - Transplantation
      - Drawer 11, Tab 19 - Plasma Cells and Tumors incl. Myeloma
      - Drawer 11, Tab 20 - Reticulum - Cell Tumors
      - Drawer 11, Tab 21 - Thymectomy, Thymic Implants
      - Drawer 11, Tab 22 - Thymus Epithelium Cultures, Leukemo-genesis in vitro
      - Drawer 11, Tab 23 - Culture of Leuk. Cells
      - Drawer 11, Tab 24 - Thyroid
      - Drawer 11, Tab 25 - Gonadectomy
      - Drawer 11, Tab 26 - Adrenalectomy, ACTH, Corticoids
      - Drawer 11, Tab 27 - Hypox and Pit. Hormones
      - Drawer 11, Tab 28 - Testosterone Inhibitions
      - Drawer 11, Tab 29 - Nuitrition
      - Drawer 11, Tab 30 - Biochemistry of Leukemic Cells
      - Drawer 11, Tab 31 - Treatment
      - Drawer 11, Tab 32 - Asparaginase
      - Drawer 12, Tab 1 - Virus from Chemically Induced Leukemias
      - Drawer 12, Tab 2 - Methods of Virus Harvest and Purification
      - Drawer 12, Tab 3 - Induction: - Viruses, etc.
      - Drawer 12, Tab 4 - Mulv, Endogenous - in vivo expression vs. strain, age, etc.
      - Drawer 12, Tab 5 - AK, C5B "Spont." (Gross)
      - Drawer 12, Tab 6 - X-Ray Virus, C57 C3H, etc.
      - Drawer 12, Tab 7 - Leuk. Virus - Immunogenic
      - Drawer 12, Tab 8 - Leuk. Virus - Kirsten
      - Drawer 12, Tab 9 - Leuk. Virus - Moloney
      - Drawer 12, Tab 10 - Mulv - Abelson
      - Drawer 12, Tab 11 - Mulv - Friend
      - Drawer 12, Tab 12 - Leuk. Virus (Rich et al.)
      - Drawer 12, Tab 13 - Leuk. Virus - (Rauscher)
      - Drawer 12, Tab 14 - Leuk. Virus - Tennant
      - Drawer 12, Tab 15 - MULV - Xenotropic and Amphotropic
      - Drawer 12, Tab 16 - MPSV: Myeloproliferative Sarcoma Virus
      - Drawer 12, Tab 17 - MULV - MCF Viruses
      - Drawer 12, Tab 18 - Nude Mice and Rats
      - Drawer 12, Tab 19 - MULV: Wild Mice
      - Drawer 12, Tab 20 - MULV-Scripps
      - Drawer 12, Tab 21 - Myeloid Virus (Graffi)
      - Drawer 12, Tab 22 - MULV - Misc.
      - Drawer 13, Tab 1 - Avian Virus
      - Drawer 13, Tab 2 - Leuk. Virus, Hamster
      - Drawer 13, Tab 3 - Leuk. - Rats
      - Drawer 13, Tab 4 - Leuk. Virus - Rats
      - Drawer 13, Tab 5 - Leuk. Virus - Cavian
      - Drawer 13, Tab 6 - Leuk. in Domestic and Farm Animals
      - Drawer 13, Tab 7 - Leuk. Virus - Feline
      - Drawer 13, Tab 8 - Retrovirus - Fish, Reptiles
      - Drawer 13, Tab 9 - Primate Type - D Viruses, (Incl. MPMV)
      - Drawer 13, Tab 10 - Non Human Primate C-Type
      - Drawer 13, Tab 11 - Poss. Human Leuk./Sarc. Viruses
      - Drawer 13, Tab 12 - Leuk. Exp. - Genetic Control of Susceptibility
      - Drawer 13, Tab 13 - Leuk. Exp. - Virus Assay Methods
      - Drawer 13, Tab 14 - Leuk. Viruses, in vitro prop.
      - Drawer 14, Tab 1 - Biochem. of Leuk. Viruses, Proteins, Enzymes, other
      - Drawer 14, Tab 2 - Reverse Transcriptase and Ribonuclease-H
      - Drawer 14, Tab 3 - Other Viral Enzymes
      - Drawer 14, Tab 4 - Hymridization - RNA/DNA. DNA/DNA
      - Drawer 14, Tab 5 - Leuk. Virus - Antigens
      - Drawer 14, Tab 6 - Immunocompetence; Infl. of Viruses, Immunosupp. Agents
      - Drawer 14, Tab 7 - Immunology of Leuk., Tumor-Specific Antigens
      - Drawer 14, Tab 8 - Virus Activation, Induction
      - Drawer 14, Tab 9 - Inhibitors of MULV Replication
      - Drawer 14, Tab 10 - Intracisternal A Particles
      - Drawer 14, Tab 11 - Leuk. Virus - Electron Microscopy
      - Drawer 14, Tab 12 - Leuk. Virus - Vaccines
      - Drawer 14, Tab 13 - Leuk. Exp. - Interferon
      - Drawer 15, Tab 1 - Transforming Genes and Transforming Gene Products
      - Drawer 15, Tab 2 - Virus - Molecular Cloning. Sequencing.
      - Drawer 15, Tab 3 - Viral Genome Mapping Studies
      - Drawer 15, Tab 4 - Expression, Transcription, and Translation Studies
      - Drawer 15, Tab 5 - Transfection
      - Drawer 15, Tab 6 - Biochem. of Leuk. Viruses, Nucleic Acids
      - Drawer 15, Tab 7 - Rescue Recombination
      - Drawer 15, Tab 8 - Leuk. Virus - Mutants and Recombinants
      - Drawer 15, Tab 9 - Transmission Studies: Vertical vs. Horizontal
      - Drawer 15, Tab 10 - Leuk. Virus - UV + X-Ray inact.
    - Drawer name: Lymphoid Tissues
      - Drawer 16, Tab 1 - Lymphoid Tissue
      - Drawer 16, Tab 2 - Lymphoid Tissue Reviews
      - Drawer 16, Tab 3 - Lymphoid Tissue Antimicrobal Role
      - Drawer 16, Tab 4 - Lymphoid Tissue Biochemistry
      - Drawer 16, Tab 5 - Lymphoid Tissue and Immunologic Resp.
      - Drawer 16, Tab 6 - Lymphoid Tissue Biol. of Lymphopoiesis
      - Drawer 16, Tab 7 - TL, Antigens Theta (O, Thy-1) and Ly-1,2
      - Drawer 16, Tab 8 - Lymphoid Tissue Carcinogens
      - Drawer 16, Tab 9 - Lymphoid Tissues Nitrogen Mustards
      - Drawer 16, Tab 10 - Lymphoid Tissues Anatomy and Histology
      - Drawer 16, Tab 11 - Lymphoid Tissues Cell and Organ Culture
      - Drawer 16, Tab 12 - Lymphoid Tissues Radiation Response
      - Drawer 16, Tab 13 - Lymphoid Tissues Physiology and Misc.
      - Drawer 16, Tab 14 - Lymphoid Tissues Nutrition
      - Drawer 16, Tab 15 - Lymphoid Tissues Thymectomy
      - Drawer 16, Tab 16 - Thymus, Thymectomy
      - Drawer 16, Tab 17 - Lymphoid Tissues Thymic Extracts
      - Drawer 16, Tab 18 - Thymus and Immunocompetence
      - Drawer 16, Tab 19 - Lymphoid Tissues Thymic Transplants
      - Drawer 16, Tab 20 - Thymus Cultures
      - Drawer 16, Tab 21 - Blastogenic Response to PHA and other stimuli
      - Drawer 16, Tab 22 - Lymphoid Tissues Hypophysectomy
      - Drawer 16, Tab 23 - Lymphoid Tissues Progesterone
      - Drawer 16, Tab 24 - Lymphoid Tissues Thyroid and TSH
      - Drawer 16, Tab 25 - Lymphoid Tissues ACTH and Adrenal Cortex
      - Drawer 16, Tab 26 - Lymphoid Tissues Pregnancy and Lactation
      - Drawer 16, Tab 27 - Lymphoid Tissues Estrogens
      - Drawer 16, Tab 28 - Lymphoid Tissues Androgens
      - Drawer 16, Tab 29 - Lymphoid Tissues Gonadectomy
      - Drawer 16, Tab 30 - Lymphoid Tissues Lactogenic
      - Drawer 16, Tab 31 - Lymphoid Tissues Gonadotropic Hormone
      - Drawer 16, Tab 32 - Lymphoid Tissues Growth Hormone
    - Drawer name: Human Lymphomas, Leukemias and Myelomas
      - Drawer 17, Tab 1 - Lymphomas and Leukemias, Cell Markers (T, B, etc.)
      - Drawer 17, Tab 2 - H.D.-Culture in Vitro
      - Drawer 17, Tab 3 - Human Myeloma Cell Lines
      - Drawer 17, Tab 4 - Lymphomas in vitro culture (and lymphoblastoid cell lines)
      - Drawer 17, Tab 5 - Lymphomas - Heterotransplants
      - Drawer 17, Tab 6 - Lymphomas - Chromosomes
    - Drawer name: Liver and Mammary Tumors, Mitosis, Metastasis, Others
      - Drawer 18, Tab 1 - Liver - Exper. Tumors
      - Drawer 18, Tab 2 - Lung - Exper. Tumors
      - Drawer 18, Tab 3 - Mammary Gland - Exper. Tumors
      - Drawer 18, Tab 4 - Marrow Culture, incl. Diffusion Chambers
      - Drawer 18, Tab 5 - Mast Cells